# **Hisham Kuntawala**



#### **OBJECTIVE**

Eager and motivated to learn new technologies related to Business and Finance. Also interested in learning IT related languages. Seeking a knowledgeable position where extensive experience can be gained and will be further developed and utilized. All for a valuable and exciting career.

# **CAREER SUMMARY**

Working experience Interpreter, Data entry Clerk, Corporate & Public relations, Social Media Promoter, Administrative Assistant and a children's Trainer. Achieved different set of soft skills and hard skills with each job experience. Soft skills included Leadership, Adaptability, Planning and Teamwork. Hard skills included MS Word, MS Excel, Python, HTML5 and CSS. Able to work individually as well as a part of a team. Pursuing to achieve relevant knowledge and experience Business Administration fields as well as IT.



ADDRESS
Jalan Melati Utama 2,
Melati Utama,
53100 Kuala Lumpur
Malaysia.



**PHONE** +6 011 1192 8191

# **EXPERIENCE**

## April 2019 - Current

Children's Trainer • Kidocode • Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

- Coaching students of age 5-18 IT related courses such as Python, App development using MIT, Web Development and electronics.
- Managing the room and making sure each student has a seat and also to ensure each row of students have enough trainers to help them.
- Developing content for Python related exercises.
- Learning new content to help the students.

#### May 2018 – August 2018

Administrative Assistant • SmartPools International • Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

- Perform Market Research on Real Estate for ongoing business model.
- Organize relevant information of existing and new clients.
- Filing (Invoices, Purchase Orders, Delivery Orders, Quotations Letters).
- Assist to check & input accounts receivable and accounts payable for new clients.
- Documentation & Editing.

# February 2018 - April 2018

Social Media Promoter • Rentanything.com • Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

- Create and design weekly posts for Facebook and Instagram.
- Publish status updates weekly on Facebook.
- Promote the startup business.

# September 2017 – November 2017

Retail Sales clerk & Manager • University • Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

- Conducted inventory analysis to determine optimal stock levels.
- Reviewed store sale numbers, cost of inventory, operational expenses, and inventory losses.
- Offered each customer top-notch, personal service and polite support to boost sales and customer satisfaction.
- Organized store merchandise racks and displays to promote and maintain visually appealing environments.
- Protected purchase items with proper bagging and wrapping to prevent damage.
- Created inviting environment for customers by maintaining store organization and cleanliness.
- Greeted customers, helped locate merchandise and suggested suitable options.
- Balanced and organized cash register by handling cash, counting change and storing coupons.
- Maintained customer satisfaction while handling product returns quickly and professionally.
- Checked for outdated and overripe items and removed them from inventory to eliminate illness and other risks.

#### June 2017 – August 2017

Corporate & Public Relations • Malaysian Reconstruction Foundation (NGO) • Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

- Develop and maintain company internet or intranet web pages.
- Identify main client groups and audiences, determine the best way to communicate.
- Develop and implement communication plans.
- Assign, supervise and review the activities of public relations staff.
- Manage communication budgets.
- Manage special events such as sponsorship of races, parties introducing new products, and others.

# April 2017 – June 2017

Interpreter (Urdu) • United Nations High Commission for Refugees (UNHCR) • Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

- Follow ethical codes that protect the confidentiality of information.
- Identify and resolve conflicts related to the meanings of words, concepts, practices, or behaviors.
- Translate messages simultaneously or consecutively into specified languages, orally or by using hand signs, maintaining message content, context, and style as much as possible.
- Proofread, edit, and revise translated materials.

# July 2016 - July 2016

Data Entry • Freelancing • Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

- Compile, sort and verify the accuracy of data before it is entered.
- Compare data with source documents, or re-enter data in verification format to detect errors.
- Store completed documents in appropriate locations.
- Processed 200 surveys.

## PROJECTS UNDERTAKEN

#### Research

- Entrepreneurship Research of a Furniture Company in Kajang 2016
- Research on Refrigerator and Washing Machine usage in KL within a specific target group

#### **Financial Statement Analysis**

• Financial Statement Analysis of years 2000-2015 of IGB Corporation

#### **EDUCATION**

# International Islamic University, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

September 2013 – June 2019

Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA), Majoring in Finance

# International Indian School, Riyadh, Saudi Arabia

April 2011 – June 2013

Commerce Stream, Passed with Distinction

# **SKILLS**

# **Computer Skills**

- Microsoft Office Suite (Word, Excel, PowerPoint) Proficient
- Windows OS (XP, 7, 8, 8.1, 10) *Proficient*

# **Information Technology Skills**

- Python Beginner
- Html Beginner
- CSS Beginner
- App Development using MIT App Inventor Beginner

## Languages

- English Speaking | Reading | Writing | (TOEFL CBT: 81)
- Hindi Speaking | Reading | Writing
- Urdu Speaking
- Gujarati Speaking

# **Professional Work Skills**

- Market Research
- Coaching
- Leadership
- Planning & Strategic Thinking
- **Efficient Communication**
- Teamwork
- Creativity
- Adaptability and Quick Learning
- Loyalty & Discretion

# REFERENCES

# Asst. Prof. Dr. Khairunisah Ibrahim

**Department of Finance** 

International Islamic University Malaysia

Tel: +6 019 266 5776 Email: <u>ikhairun@iium.edu.my</u>

#### Dr. Nor Azizan Che Embi

**Department of Finance** 

International Islamic University Malaysia

**Tel:** +6 03 6196 4736

Email: izanebbm@iium.edu.my

# **Nurul Damia Mohamad Sofian**

**Senior Executive Public Relations & Administration** 

Malaysian Reconstruction Foundation (PPAB-08/2016)

**Tel:** +6 013 999 1356

Email: nuruldamia@myref.org.my

# Mr. Mohd Hannan

**Business Development** 

SmartPools Sdn Bhd

**Tel:** +6 010 267 0452

Email: hannan@smartpools.com.my